Guide to the Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1925-1985 AIS.1978.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Municipal Governments, 1929-1975; II.
  - Altoona, "A Study of the Altoona Fire Department", August, 1968
  - Altoona, "Mid-Year Analysis – Altoona Finances – 1968", July, 1968
  - Altoona, "Third Quarter Analysis – Altoona Finances- 1968", October, 1968
  - Altoona, "Third Quarter Analysis – Altoona Finances – 1969", October, 1969
  - Altoona, "Residential Garbage Disposal City of Altoona", April, 1963
  - Altoona, "Methods of Financing Public Parking for City Parking Committee City of Altoona", June, 1966
  - Altoona, "Organization and Procedural Controls for Purchasing", September, 1968
  - Altoona, "Comparison of Twelve Third Class Cities", November, 1967
  - Altoona, "Altoona in Focus Improved Fiscal Practices Shown in League's Analysis of 28 Western Pennsylvania Third Class Cities", January, 1964
  - Altoona, "Fiscal Review and Preview: 1970-1980 City of Altoona", July, 1975
  - Altoona, "A Feasibility Study of Adoption of the County Assessment by the City of Altoona", June, 1976
  - Altoona, "A Study of the Public Off-Street Parking Facilities", January, 1968
  - Altoona, "A Study of the Present and Future Parking Facilities of the City of Altoona", February, 1969
  - Altoona, "A Fiscal Study of the Altoona Area Public Library", June, 1972
  - Altoona, "Adoption of the County Assessment by the City of Altoona", October, 1968
  - Altoona, "Specifications for Hospitalization Medical-Surgical, and Major Medical Coverage for the City of Altoona", November, 1971
  - Altoona, "Community Development – City of Altoona", November, 1966
  - Altoona, "Analysis of City of Altoona Firemen's Pension Plan", April, 1969
  - Altoona City: "Confidential Report on the Preliminary Financial Study of the City of Altoona as Related to the 1948 Budget", March, 1948
  - Altoona, "City of Altoona Report on the Accounting System Survey and Recommendations Volume I Text", April, 1949
  - Altoona, "The Feasibility of Municipal Ownership and Operation of Off-Street Parking Facilities in the City of Altoona", May, 1960
  - Altoona, "A Six Months Review of Fiscal Operations City of Altoona", August, 1960
  - Altoona, "A Preliminary Survey of the Earned Income Tax Office in the Department of Accounts and Finance", August, 1961
  - Altoona, "A Survey of the Accounting and Bookkeeping Procedures in the Department of Accounts and Finance", March, 1961
  - Altoona, "City of the Altoona Water and Sewer Department 1961 Financial Experience 1962 Budget", February, 1962
  - Altoona, "General Liability Insurance Specifications", June, 1964
  - Altoona, "Nine Months of Altoona's 1951 Budget", November, 1951
  - Altoona, "Confidential Report on the Altoona Water Department", March, 1954
  - Altoona, "Report on the Department of Streets and Public Improvements of the City of Altoona", June, 1952
  - Altoona, "Mass Transportation for Altoona, Pennsylvania", July, 1958
  - Ambridge, "A Financial Analysis of Ambridge Borough Funds 1938-1943", January, 1945
  - Ambridge, "A Review of the 1945 Budget of the Borough of Ambridge with Recommendation's", February, 1945
  - Ambridge, "A Report on Parking and Traffic Problems in the Business Area of Ambridge Borough", April, 1953
  - Antis, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications for Antis Township Board of Supervisors", August, 1975
  - Antis, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications for Antis Township Board of Supervisors", August, 1975
  - Antis, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications for Antis Township Board of Supervisors", August, 1978
  - Antis, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications for Antis Township Board of Supervisors", August, 1978
  - Apollo, "A Financial Analysis of the Borough of Apollo", October, 1961
  - Apollo, "An Analysis and Projection of Apollo Borough's Fiscal Operation", March, 1980
  - Apollo, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection Apollo Borough 1968-1978", October, 1973
  - Apollo, "Traffic and Parking Survey", January, 1956
  - Applewold, "A Financial Analysis of the Borough of Applewold", June, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Arnold, "City of Arnold A Review of Financial Trends 1944-1958", July, 1955
  - Arnold, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection City of Arnold 1967-1978", March, 1973
  - Arnold, "Review of Proposed Plans for the Treatment and Disposal of Sewage in the City of Arnold", April, 1958
  - Arnold, "Procedures of the Office of the City Treasure City of Arnold, Pennsylvania", January, 1956
  - Aspinwall, "Financial and Operating Analysis Aspinwall Electric System", April, 1966
  - Aspinwall, "Fiscal Review and Forecast Borough of Aspinwall", February, 1967
  - Aspinwall, "Borough of Aspinwall Accounting System Survey", June, 1972
  - Avonmore, "Borough of Avonmore A Suggested Accounting System", October, 1964
  - Avonmore, "An Analysis of the Financial Operations of the Borough of Avonmore", October, 1954
  - Back Mountain, "Back Mountain Police Service", March, 1964
  - Baden, "Borough of Baden an Administrative Survey", March, 1969
  - Baden, "A Manual of Procedure for Recommended Changes in Accounting System", August, 1949
  - Baden, "Police Pension Funds Borough of Baden", December, 1957
  - Beaver Falls, "A Report on Parking and Traffic Problems in the Business Area of the City of Beaver Falls", April, 1953
  - Beaver Falls, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection City of Beaver Falls 1966-1975", November, 1971
  - Beaver Falls, "Report on the 1946 Proposed Budget of Beaver Falls", January, 1946
  - Beaver Falls, "City of Beaver Falls A Study of its Financial Operations 1942-1947 and the 1948 Budget", October, 1948
  - Beaver, "Report on a Self-Administered Police Pension Plan Borough of Beaver", February, 1969
  - Bell Vernon, "Financial Analysis of the Borough of Belle Vernon", September, 1959
  - Bell Vernon, "Time for Decision Values in Municipal Consolidation", May, 1963
  - Bethel, "Survey of Accounting Procedures and Practices", April, 1956
  - Bethel, "Borough of Bethel Financing Sewage Collection System and Treatment Facilities", May, 1956
  - Big Beaver, "Borough Organization in a Newly Incorporated Borough", December, 1959
  - Blairsville, "Outline of a Simplified Accounting System Borough of Blairsville", August, 1963
  - Blawnox, "Borough of Blawnox Fiscal Analysis and projection 1968-1977", August, 1973
  - Blawnox, "Blawnox Accounting System", October, 1977
  - Bloomsburg, "Town of Bloomsburg Accounting System and Budget Control", August, 1956
  - Brackenridge, "Brackenridge Water Rate Study (Preliminary)", January, 1968
  - Brackenridge, "Financial Plan for Street Improvement Program", May, 1972
  - Braddock, "Comparative Financial Study of the 1947 Operations", December, 1948
  - Braddock Hills, "A Road Program for Braddock Hills Borough", July, 1960
  - Bradford, "City of Bradford Survey of Treasurer's Office", July, 1949
  - Bradford, "Report on Existing Methods for the Collection and Disposal of Garbage and Other Refuse Together with an Analysis of the Rate Structure", November, 1949
  - Bradford, "Report on the Best Method of Operating the Water Utility Under an 'Authority' Mechanism", January, 1954
  - Bradford, "Pension Funds Report on a Study of the Financial Status and Operation of the City's Three Pension Funds", September, 1951
  - Bradford, "Interim Report on Agency Interest in Development of a Shared Human Services Complex for Bradford, Pennsylvania", June, 1979
  - Bradford, "Police Department Report on Comparison of Present and Proposed Working Schedules", July, 1951
  - Bradford, "A Report on the Population Census of Bradford Township McKean County, Pennsylvania", April, 1949
  - Bridgeville, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications for Bridgeville Borough", October, 1974
  - Bridgeville, "Official Bid Notice Borough of Bridgeville Invitation to Bid on Purchase of Computer Software and Hardware", June, 1988
  - Bridgeville, "Fiscal Impact Study of Swimming Pool Construction for Borough of Bridgeville", March, 1964
  - Bristol, "Analysis of Facts Relating to Reclassification of Bristol Township", September, 1950
  - Bristol, "Report of the Survey of Bristol Borough Municipal Water System", July, 1951
  - Brownsville, "Report on Suggested off Street Parking Facilities to be Constructed in the Dunlap's Creek Area of Brownsville, Pennsylvania", July, 1951
  - Brownsville, "Comparative Analysis of the Size, Salaries and Fringe Benefits of the Borough of Brownsville's Police Department", August, 1979
  - Burgettstown, "A Simplified Accounting System (Including Budgetary Controls)", June, 1947
  - Burgettstown, "Analysis of the Fiscal Affairs of the Borough of Burgettstown", December, 1946
  - Butler, "Merger Study Butler City and Butler Township A Decision for the Electorate", March, 1965
  - Butler, "Downtown Revitalization Alternatives for Funding the Downtown Butler Renaissance Commission", November, 1984
  - Butler, "1963 Budget Compared to 1962 Budget and Expenditures", January, 1963
  - Butler,"A Survey Concerning Purchasing", October, 1954
  - Butler, "Purchasing Procedure", March, 1955
  - Butler, "1960 Budget and Tax Structure Compared to 1959 Budget and Expenditures", January, 1960
  - Butler, "1964 Budget Compared to 1963 Budget and Expenditures and Butler City Compared to Western Pennsylvania's 28 Third Class Cities – 1961 & 1962", January, 1964
  - Butler, "Report on Sewage Treatment", September, 1955
  - Butler, "City of Butler Fiscal Analysis in Brief: 1971-1976", March, 1976
  - Butler, "An Analysis of Fire and Casualty Insurance Coverage", October, 1948
  - Butler, "A Proposed Budget Form", December, 1966
  - Butler, "A Proposed Position Classification Plan for Butler City", January, 1966
  - Butler, "A Report Concerning Liened Taxes of the City of Butler", October, 1940
  - Butler, "City of Butler Fiscal Review and Forecast 1961-1971", August, 1966
  - Butler, "A Study of the Occupation Tax", June, 1940
  - Butler, "Butler City's Fiscal Posture Past, Present, and a Look Ahead a Commentary with Supporting Exhibits", July, 1969
  - Butler,"Organization and Regulations Governing the City of Butler Police Department", September, 1962 (Box 12)
  - Butler, "Estimated 1964 Financial Operations and the 1965 Budget", January, 1965
  - Butler, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications City of Butler", May, 1972
  - Butler, "The Pennsylvania Economy League Surveys the Butler Public Library", October, 1941
  - Butler, "Organizations and Regulations Governing the City of Butler Police Department", February, 1967
  - Butler, "Butler City Retirement Plan for Non-Uniformed Employees", October, 1973
  - Butler, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications City of Butler", March, 1968
  - Butler, "Police Pension Survey", May, 1965
  - Butler, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications City of Butler", April, 1971
  - Butler, "Municipal Pension Survey", August, 1965
  - Butler, "Report on the Budget of the City of Butler 1941-1945, 1950-1951 Butler County Committee", December, 1950
  - Butler, "Firemen's Pension Survey", August, 1965
  - Butler,"Analysis of Garbage and Refuse Disposal Methods", April, 1950
  - Butler,"Report on the Butler Township 1964 Financial Operations and the 1965 Township Budget", June, 1965
  - Butler, "Report on Sewer Flooding, Recommended Relief Measures and Related Subjects", July, 1957
  - Butler, "Review of Police Pension Plan and other Fringe Benefits", March, 1966
  - Butler, "Position Classification and Pay Plan", October, 1973
  - Butler, "Municipal Employee Retirement Systems", May, 1966
  - Butler,"Report Upon the Effectuation of the Plan a Part of the Comprehensive Plan", January, 1959
  - Butler, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications Township of Butler and the Butler Township Volunteer Fire Companies", February, 1969
  - Butler, "Report on the Budget of Butler Township 1941-1942-1944", September, 1944
  - Butler, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications Township of Butler and Butler Township Volunteer Fire Companies", February, 1969
  - Butler, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection 1975-1983", October, 1980
  - Butler, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications", January, 1971
  - Butler: "Butler Township the 1966 Financial Operations and the 1967 Financial Budget", August, 1967
  - Canonsburg, "Report on an Accounting System", November, 1944
  - Canonsburg, "Canonsburgh's Fiscal Helath Financial Analysis and projections 1973-1981", November, 1978
  - Canonsburg, "An Administrative Study of Canonsburg Borough Government", February, 1979
  - Canonsburg: "A Report on the Traffic and Parking Problem", June, 1957
  - Canton, "1945 Budget Analysis", August, 1945
  - Canton, "1946 Budget Report", April, 1946
  - Canton, "A Simplified Accounting System (Including Budgetary Controls)", June, 1947
  - Canton, "An Analysis of the 1947 Budget", March, 1947
  - Carmichaels, "Carmichaels Municipal Authority Accounting System and Management Recommendations", July, 1978
  - Carnegie, "Borough of Carnegie Survey and Recommendations 1955 Budget", December, 1954
  - Charleroi, "Borough of Charleroi Financial Analysis 1940 to 1945 and 1946 Budget Estimates", April, 1946
  - Charleroi, "An Analysis of the Financial Operations of the Borough of Charleroi", September, 1959
  - Charleroi, "Post-War Financial Review Charleroi Borough 1945-1951", February, 1952
  - Charleroi, "An Accounting System for the Borough of Charleroi Volume I Text, Volume II Exhibits", December, 1961
  - Charleroi, "Borough of Charleroi to Face Fiscal Problems in the Eighties Fiscal Analysis and Projections 1975-1983", October, 1980
  - Chartiers, "Fiscal Review and Review: 1970-1979", September, 1975
  - Clairton City, "Financial Analysis 1939-1949", June, 1949
  - Chippewa, "Which Form of Government?", July, 1961
  - Clairton City, "Financial Analysis and Forecast 1957-1967", April, 1963
  - Clairton City, "The Fiscal Posture of the City of Clairton Past, Present, and Future", December, 1969
  - Clairton City, "Evaluation of 1972 Budget", February, 1972
  - Clairton City, "City of Clairton Financial Analysis and Forecast, 1957-1967", April, 1963
  - Clairton City, "Department of the City Treasurer Accounting System", April, 1972
  - Clairton City, "Financial and Administrative Analysis of the City of Clairton 1949-1952", September, 1953
  - Claysville, "A Simplified Accounting System (Including Budgetary Controls", July, 1960
  - Clearfield, "Fiscal Review and Preview: 1977-1987 Coungy of Clearfield", June, 1982
  - Coatesville, "Opportunity Knocks in the Coatesville Area a Report on Refuse Disposal Problems in the Coatesville Area of Chester County", July, 1954
  - Collier, "Collier Township Renewal Study Prepared for Redevelopment Authority of Allegheny County", December, 1964
  - Collier, "Engineering Feasibility Report Collier Township Renewal Area", September, 1964
  - Connellsville, "Memorandum Report on Connellsville City Finances January 1, 1959 – October 1, 1959", October, 1959 (Box 13)
  - Connellsville, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection City of Connellsville 1963-1971", August, 1968
  - Connellsville, "Financial Review and Recommendations Concerning the 1955 Budget", November, 1954
  - Connellsville, "Hyatt Medical Management Services, Inc.", January, 1981
  - Connellsville, "Fiscal Analysis, 1965-1966 ad Forecast for 1967", October, 1966
  - Connellsville, "A Feasibility Study of Connellsville State General Hospital", April, 1974
  - Connellsville, "Description of City Clerk's Position: Options for Centralized Administration", April, 1976
  - Connellsville, "An Administrative Report", October, 1980
  - Connellsville, "The City of Connellsville an Analysis of the 1962 Budget", January, 1962
  - Connellsville, "An Administrative Study", January, 1963
  - Connellsville, "Report on Financial Resources", October, 1944
  - Connellsville, "Fiscal and Background Data", September, 1971
  - Connellsville, "Research and Survey Report", 1958
  - Connellsville, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications", May 1969
  - Cranberry Township: "Multiperil Insurance Specifications", December, 1972
  - Connellsville, "Report on Financial Resources", October, 1944
  - Darby Township: "Administrative Survey", January, 1957
  - Dawson, "A Water Study for the Borough of Dawson", January, 1954
  - Dormont Borough, "Report of Borough of Dormont Accounting System", January, 1955
  - Donora, "An Analysis of the Various Parking Proposal Under Consideration", February, 1958
  - Donora, "Accounting System Survey and Recommendations", April, 1955
  - Donora, "Accounting System Survey and Recommendations", March, 1948
  - Donora, "Financial Analysis of the Borough of Donora 1938-1943", November, 1944
  - Donora, "A Fiscal Analysis and Projection for the Borough of Donora 1956-1971", December, 1966
  - Downingtown, "Curing the Water Problems of Downingtown Borough", August, 1955
  - Downingtown, "Looks Ahead the Borough Council of Downingtown Studies its Administrative Problems", May, 1951
  - Downingtown, "One Year After: A Progress Report on Accomplishments of Downingtown Borough Council in Implementation Recommendations of Economy League Survey of 1951", October, 1952
  - Duquesne, "Financial Analysis 1936-1946 and Future Projections", December, 1947
  - Duquesne, "Declining Revenue Base Poses Challenge to City's Fiscal Operations: Fiscal Analysis and Projections 1973-1982", September, 1978
  - East Butler, "East Butler Borough a Financial and Administrative Study", October, 1967
  - East Deer, "Analysis of Insurance", February, 1955
  - East Deer, "Review Operation and Rate Schedule Water Department", Unknown
  - East Deer, "Financial Study of East Deer Township 1940-1945 and Projection to 1960", January, 1947
  - East Deer, "Report on the East Deer Township 1948 Budget", March, 1948
  - East Deer, "A Financial Review and Projection 1967-1973", November, 1972
  - East Deer, "Report on an Analysis of the Rate Structure and Operating Costs of the Water Department of East Deer Township", May, 1947
  - East Deer, "Study of the Rates and Regulations East Deer Township Water Department", 1959
  - East Deer, "Water System Extension", February, 1966
  - East Huntington Township: "Analysis of Financial Operations and Economic Background", August, 1967
  - East McKeesport, "Financing the Sewage Disposal System", May, 1959
  - East McKeesport, "A Financial Analysis of East McKeesport Borough 1939-1948 and the 1949 Budget", December, 1949
  - Easton, "Police Administration in the City of Easton", August, 1948
  - Easton, "The Easton Public Library a Survey", May, 1955
  - Emsworth, "Emsworth Borough Financial Survey", December, 1957
  - Ellwood, "Ellwood City Faces Fiscal Challenges in the Eighties Fiscal Analysis and Projection 1976-1982", March, 1980
  - Ellwood, "Electric Fund Accounting Improvements Borough of Ellwood City", September, 1980
  - Ellwood, "Borough of Ellwood City Police Pension Fund", June, 1958
  - Etna: "Financial and Operating Analysis Etna Borough Electric Plant", September, 1959
  - Etna: "Borough of Etna Police Pension System", January, 1958
  - Export: "A Parking Lot for Export", June, 1960
  - Farrell, "Comparison of Garbage and Refuse Disposal Costs", December, 1954
  - Farrell, "Fiscal Review and Preview: 1969-1980", October, 1975
  - Farrell, "Proposed Monthly Financial Report for the City of Farrell", January, 1968
  - Farrell, "Financial Analysis – User Fee Fund and Sewage Treatment Rate Analysis", November, 1982
  - Farrell, "A Financial Review of the City of Farrell", June, 1962
  - Farrell, "Financial and Administrative Analysis of the City of Farrell Mercer County, Pennsylvania 1947-1954", October, 1955
  - Farrell, "Sewage User Fee Study", October, 1977
  - Farrell, "Thirteen Years of Financial Operations 1933-1945", April, 1946 (Box 14)
  - Farrell, "Sewer User Fund and Rate Analysis", August, 1979
  - Farrell, "Farrell's Expenditures for 1946 Its Plans for 1947", February, 1947
  - Ford, "A Self-Administered Police Pension Plan", June, 1958
  - Ford, "An Analysis and Projection of Ford City Borough's Fiscal Operations", November, 1979
  - Ford, "Study of Operations of Both the Water and Electric Plants", September, 1955
  - Ford, "Refuse Disposal Study", April, 1957
  - Ford, "Financial Analysis Borough of Ford City", January, 1956
  - Ford, "Study of Water Facilities for the Borough of Ford City", October, 1952
  - Ford, "Parking and Traffic Survey Ford City Borough", January, 1956
  - Ford,"Solid Waste Collection and Disposal Practices", January, 1977
  - Ford, "Ford City Electric System A Study of the Impact of the Sale of a Municipal Utility", March, 1961
  - Ford, "A Review of the Ford City Police Pension Plan", November, 1961
  - Ford, "A Year of Decision A Review of the 1964 Financial Operations and the 1965 Budget for the Borough of Ford City", June, 1965
  - Ford, "The League Studies the Insurance Program of Ford City Borough", March, 1966
  - Forward, "Insurance Specifications", September, 1970
  - Forward, "Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications", September, 1970
  - Franklin, "Problems Relating to the Collection of the Earned Income Tax and Delinquent Taxes", October, 1965
  - Franklin, "Facts and Figures of Finance 1952-1968 Township of Franklin", January, 1963
  - Franklin, "The Collection of Taxes", September, 1965
  - Frazer, "Preliminary Report Proposed Water Supply and Distribution System Township of Frazer", November, 1965
  - Freeport, "Tax and Financial Analysis 1945-1953", January, 1954
  - Green Tree, "Fiscal Analysis 1958-1962 and Proposed Bond Issues", May, 1963
  - Green Tree, "Fiscal Analysis and Projection", August, 1966
  - Greensburg, "Sewage Service Rate Study", August, 1966
  - Greensburg, "Memorandum on Off-Street Parking for Greensburg", October, 1945
  - Greensburg, "Report on the 1944 and 1945 Budgets City of Greensburg", February, 1945
  - Greensburg, "Report on Reuse Collection and Disposal for the City of Greensburg", April, 1944
  - Greensburg, "Position Classification and Job Description Study City of Greensburg", August, 1965
  - Greensburg, "An Administrative Study of the City Government of Greensburg", December, 1963
  - Greensburg, "Review of the 1946 Budget and 1945 Fiscal Operations City of Greensburg", February, 1946
  - Greensburg, "Mid-Year for 1966 Finances", July, 1966
  - Greensburg, "1967 Financial Operations at Mid-Year", August, 1967
  - Greensburg, "Sewage Service Rate Study Greater Greensburg Sewage Authority", August, 1966
  - Greensburg, "Report on Revenue Accounting for the City of Greensburg", June, 1943
  - Greensburg, "Report on Disbursement Accounting City of Greensburg", July, 1943
  - Greensburg, "The Problem of Real Estate Assessment in the City of Greensburg", July, 1957
  - Greensburg, "Economic Base Information Report", March, 1959
  - Greensburg, "Employee Retirement Systems", June, 1962
  - Greensburg, "Financial Operations 1960-1964", March, 1964
  - Greensburg, "1963 Financial Operations at Mid-Year", July, 1963
  - Greensburg, "Operations of the Greensburg Bus Terminal a Study and Recommendations", December, 1955
  - Greensburg, "Wage and Salary Survey City of Greensburg", June, 1961
  - Greensburg, "Memorandum on Financial Reporting Procedures of the Greenburg Recreation Board with Observations on some Administrative Conditions", February, 1951
  - Greensburg, "Recommendations Relating to Revenue Reporting and Control City of Greensburg", December, 1957
  - Greensburg, "Financial Budget Review and Projection for 1958", July, 1958
  - Greensburg, "Mid-Year Review and Projection of 1959 Budget", July, 1959
  - Greensburg, "Mid-Year Review and Projection of 1962 Budget", July, 1962
  - Greensburg, "Financial Effect of Proposed Bond Issues City of Greensburg", September, 1952